Gene Basset Papers
Gene Basset Papers
- Cartoons, 1,319 items
  - Cartoons, 1966, Dec (Oversize 7)
    Dec 9: God rest ye merry, spacemen: nuclear weapons, Soviet Union
    Dec 12: Quit bugging me!: Robert F. Kennedy, J. Edgar Hoover, espionage
    Dec 14: Wal, shut mah great big mouth!: civil rights, Lester Maddox
    Dec 15: Of course, we'll still keep our high credibility rating: Bill Moyers, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Dec 19: Let's face it, Mr. Prime Minister....I'm not what I used to be: Britain, Harold Wilson
    Dec 20: Here we go again: peace
    Dec 22: For temporary relief: peace
    Dec 24: Good news...you've dropped nine-tenths of one percent: inflation
    Dec 24: Kamakaze pilot: drunk driving
    Dec 28: Don't you know a military target from a civilian one: Vietnam War, weapons
    Dec 30: You'll have to wait your turn, Mr. Romney: elections, George Romney
    Dec 31: Bang, Bang!: Adam Clayton Powell
    Dec: The juggernaut: traffic fatalities
    Dec: Go West: Mao Zedong, Russia
    Dec: Hey amigos...the finish line is here!: Puerto Rico, Cuba
    Dec: What do you ever do for civil rights: Adam Clayton Powell, James Meredith
  - Cartoons, 1967, Jan (Oversize 7)
    Jan 3: For the New Year, I recommend a thorough overhaul: Walter Reuther, George Meany
    Jan 4: In 8 years Fidel has sort of grown on us: Fidel Castro, Cuba
    Jan 5: Surrender or else!: Vietnam War, peace
    Jan 6: There, that's more like it!: Lyndon B. Johnson (and his portrait by Peter Hurd)
    Jan 9: What do you think this is...a Democratic Party?: Eugene McCarthy
    Jan 10: Escalation: Lyndon B. Johnson, programs
    Jan 12: No, no, honeychile...I'll lead and you follow: Republican Party, Democratic Party
    Jan 14: Help...I'm a prisoner in an electoral college!:
    Jan 16: ...and now the Super Duper Bowl: Great Society, Vietnam War
    Jan 17: Go ahead, launch one and see what happens: Gerald R. Ford, Lyndon B. Johnson, John McCormack
    Jan 18: Keep to the right, Lurleen honey: George Wallace, Lurleen Wallace
    Jan 19: Lift that barge, tote that bale...: government spending, economy
    Jan 20: State of the union: Gerald R. Ford, Everett Dirksen
    Jan 22: I haven't got the heart: Congress, budget, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Jan 23: Big man on campus: University of California, Clark Kerr, Ronald Reagan
    Jan 24: The budget
    Jan 26: My position on your entering the common market has softened a bit: Charles De Gaulle, Harold Wilson
    Jan 28: And now they belong to the heavens: space exploration, Gus Grissom, Edward White, Roger Chaffee
    Jan 28: Cheapskate!: Robert McNamara, nuclear weapons, anti-missile systems
  - Cartoons, 1967, Feb (Oversize 7)
    Feb 1: Hey, look what I found on the Champs-Elysees!: Charles De Gaulle, Robert F. Kennedy, Vietnam War
    Feb 2: ....and holding!: space exploration
    Feb 3: He says he's still waiting for a real one: Ho Chi Minh, peace, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Feb 4: Take it from an expert...this is dangerous!: Soviet Union
    Feb 6: Hurry, comrades...the Chinese are coming!: china, Soviet Union
    Feb 16: Look who's running!: Richard Nixon, George Romney
    Feb 23: I understand the CIA has withdrawn their subsidies: closed businesses
    Feb 24: Your seat, sir: Adam Clayton Powell
    Feb 25: Not so sacred anymore: India, elections
    Feb 27: Out we go,...into the Wild Blue Yonder...: Air Force Academy, cheating scandal
  - Cartoons, 1967, Mar (Oversize 7)
    Mar 1: After you, Noble sir: Senate ethics reform
    Mar 6: I see no basis now for optimism on Viet Nam: U. Thant
    Mar 8: ....and this is the latest addition to the rogues, er ha, I mean Teamster's portrait gallery: Jimmy Hoffa, Dave Beck
    Mar 22: Say, who's directing this show?: Lyndon B. Johnson, Nguyen Cao Ky
  - Cartoons, 1967, Apr (Oversize 7)
    Apr 10: Who gave you the right to drive like me?: Teamsters
    Apr 12: It's official...you died from a case of lingering carelessness: space exploration, Gus Grissom, Edward White, Roger Chaffee
    Apr 15: You gotta accentuate the positive, eliminate the negative: Hubert Humphrey, press
    Apr 17: No need for alarm, Mr. President. The enemy beachheads are surrounded: J. Edgar Hoover, demonstrations
    Apr 24: Greek ruins: Greece, democracy
    Apr 27: From America with love: Alexey Kosygin, Leonid Ilyich Brezhnev, Svetlana Stalin
    Apr 28: [Editors, note: no caption with this cartoon.]: Senate ethics, Christopher Dodd
  - Cartoons, 1967, May (Oversize 7)
    May 6: [Editors, note: no caption with this cartoon.]: Lyndon B. Johnson, railroad industry, strikes
    May 10: Solidarity: Central Intelligence Agency, AFL-CIO
    May 13: What a race, folks...nose to nose: Richard Nixon, George Romney
    May 16: ...Meanwhile back at the gym...: Soviet Union, Vietnam China, Lyndon B. Johnson, Mao Zedong, Leonid Ilyich Brezhnev, Nguyen Cao Ky
    May 17: The patriot: taxes, armed forces
    May 19: Sword swallower: Middle East
    May 26: Raising the roof: Congress, national debt
    May 27: Bottleneck: Israel
  - Cartoons, 1967, Jun (Oversize 7)
    Jun 2: Sit tight...we're figuring out how to save you: Israel Lyndon B. Johnson
    Jun 5: Patient's dilemma: Middle East, United Nations
    Jun 12: Maybe we should have caught him: Middle East, United Nations
    Jun 15: Ammo: Ghettoes, Stokley Carmichael
    Jun 19: Some security: nuclear weapons, China
    Jun 25: Great job!: Vietnam War, Middle East, Barry Goldwater, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Jun 26: Getting to know you: Lyndon B. Johnson, Alexey Kosygin
    Jun 27: En garde!: Soviet Union, Romania, Alexey Kosygin
    Jun 28: Relax...Doctor knows best!: health care
    Jun 29: ...just checking my investments: Alexey Kosygin, Cuba, Fidel Castro. Middle East
  - Cartoons, 1967, Jul (Oversize 7)
    Jul 1: Veep, veep: Nguyen Cao Ky, Vietnam War
    Jul 3: Daddy, all is forgiven!: Lyndon B. Johnson, Democratic Party
    Jul 3: Companion: Vietnam War
    Jul 10: Progress report: Vietnam War, Congo, Nigeria, Hong Kong, Middle East
    Jul 11: High noon: auto industry, United Auto Workers
    Jul 14: There now, have I restored your self respect?: Soviet Union, Abdel Gamal Nasser
    Jul 15: We're making tremendous progress!: Vietnam War, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Jul 17: The assassins: racial violence, Newark
    Jul 19: It's about time you boys learned how to run a railroad: Congress, railroad industry, unions
    Jul 20: All in favor of the Thieu-Ky ticket, raise your hands: Vietnam War, elections
    Jul 26: Greetings: Charles De Gaulle, Lester Bowles Pearson, Canada
    Jul 27: Business as usual: Democratic Party, Republican Party
    Jul 28: Briefing: Vietnam War, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Jul 31: Brother, can you spare a few thousand?: Vietnam War, Lyndon B. Johnson, armed forces
  - Cartoons, 1967, Aug (Oversize 8)
    Aug 18: Hand it over...I'm an expert on the subject!: Congress, gun control
    Aug 22: Home delivery: unions, United States Postal Service
    Aug 27: Freedom from the press: Vietnam War
    Aug 29: You've only been tossed for another loss...the game's not over!: cost of living, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Aug 30: Want to take a trip?: Shirley Temple, Republican Party
  - Cartoons, 1967, Sep (Oversize 7)
    Sep 2: We're following a trend: Lyndon B. Johnson, steel industry
    Sep 2: Honest differences of opinion have been blown out of proportion: Lyndon B. Johnson, Robert McNamara
    Sep 6: Bird in hand: Nguyen Cao Ky, Nguyen Van Thieu, peace
    Sep 7: School daze: teachers, strikes, bussing,
    Sep 9: Your trouble is you can't recognize the truth when you see or hear it: George Romney, Robert McNamara, Vietnam War
    Sep 11: I'm still in the picture: George Romney, Republican Party
    Sep 13: The new season: teacher's strike
    Sep 14: Now here's my plan: Ronald Reagan
    Sep 19: Don't worry...this one'll sort of grow on you, too!: taxes, Vietnam War, Robert McNamara, anti-missile systems
    Sep 21: I'm not so sure this is an emergency: inflation, Congress, taxes
    Sep 26: The gym fighter: Organization of American States, Fidel Castro
    Sep 28: You heard me...I'm declaring another disaster area here!: Lyndon B. Johnson, Vietnam War, demonstrations
    Sep 29: Hold it, maestro...you forgot your bow!: Congress, government spending
  - Cartoons, 1967, Oct (Oversize 8)
    Oct 4: Your problem, mon ami, is you're obsolete: France, farming, Charles De Gaulle
    Oct 7: When are you going to hit the brakes?: Congress, inflation, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Oct 9: Man, have you got a case of a communicable disease!: Vietnam War, NATO, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Oct 10: The Rockefeller magic: Nelson Rockefeller, Richard Nixon, Ronald Reagan, George Romney
    Oct 11: You don't expect me to sacrifice my own flesh and blood: Congress, government spending, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Oct 12: Hello Hanoi?...negotiate or I'll turn my man loose!: Vietnam War, Nguyen Van Thieu
    Oct 14: Slightly off target: taxes, Congress, government spending
    Oct 17: You're doing great, kid...They ain't laid a glove on you: Vietnam War, Dean Rusk, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Oct 19: I understand Venus is too hot to sustain human life: Vietnam War
    Oct 20: We don't want you to catch one of those dread foreign diseases: trade, consumers
    Oct 21: He refuses to walk the plank!: Republican Party, Democratic Party, Lyndon B. Johnson, Vietnam War
    Oct 24: Neither protests, nor Marches, nor doves, nor gloomy polls stays this courier from this endless rounds: Lyndon B. Johnson, Vietnam War
    Oct 26: He hit me back!: United Nations, Israel, Abdel Gamal Nasser
    Oct 27: Stop! You wanna make him mad?: inflation, economy, Congress, government spending
    Oct 28: Altitude bothering you, dearie?: cost of living
    Oct 30: By jove...I think I May have discovered something: Abdel Gamal Nasser, King Hussein of Jordan, Israel
    Oct 31: There will be no Nobel Peace Prize for 1966 or 1967: peace
  - Cartoons, 1967, Nov
    Nov 9: Suppose they're trying to tell us something?: H. Rap Brown, Stokely Carmichael
    Nov 10: America's biggest payload: inflation
    Nov 13: Why don't we let the donkey decide: Eugene McCarthy, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Nov 15: Good news, Coach...I've decided to make another comeback: Harold Stassen, Republican Party
    Nov 18: Next question, please: Lyndon B. Johnson
    Nov 21: Hey, everybody...I've made my decision: George Romney
    Nov 24: Follow that car!: crime
    Nov 27: Phew...we hope!: Cyprus, peace
    Nov 28: Le French barbecue: Charles De Gaulle, Canada, Britain, Israel
    Nov 30: Watch it, kid...or I'll unleash Hubert on you again!: Lyndon B. Johnson, Hubert Humphrey, Robert F. Kennedy
  - Cartoons, 1967, Dec (Oversize 8)
    Dec 1: Primary target: Eugene McCarthy, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Dec 7: He's at a difficult age: Benjamin Spock
    Dec 8: [Editors: no caption.]: wages, prices
    Dec 12: Hey Whitey, I'm back: Stokely Carmichael
    Dec 14: Hey, who do you think you are...another Hercules?: Greece, Constantine II
    Dec 16: Hold it, Mac...your license has been revoked: federal employees, nepotism
    Dec 18: Thanks for taking it easy on my boy: Lyndon B. Johnson, Congress
    Dec 19: Beat you to it, Charlie: inflation, Charles De Gaulle
    Dec 20: Very well...if the King won't lend us we'll do without him: Greece
    Dec 21: Follow me and we might even score on this play: Lyndon B. Johnson, Vietnam War, peace, Nguyen Van Thieu
    Dec 22: We are indeed united on how to deal with the Viet Cong: Lyndon B. Johnson, Nguyen Van Thieu, Vietnam War
    Dec 22: ...and remember, I'm the leader!: Republican Party, Barry Goldwater
    Dec 23: Wring out the old, bring in the new: Charles De Gaulle, New Year's
    Dec 27: You mean this is it?: New Year's, war
    Dec 28: C'mon, man...this is no time to think!: Lyndon B. Johnson, Cambodia, Vietnam War
    Dec 29: You got a great future, Kid, if you don't panic: inflation, economy
    Dec 30: Traffic cop: Cambodia, Norodom Sihanouk
  - Cartoons, 1968, Jan (Oversize 8)
    Jan 3: Emergency: Lyndon B. Johnson, U.S. Dollar
    Jan 4: What do you expect in only nine years?: Fidel Castro, Cuba
    Jan 5: I don't need any help: Lyndon B. Johnson, Charles De Gaulle
    Jan 12: Tough course: Eugene McCarthy, George Romney
    Jan 13: See, the sword is mightier than the pen!: Soviet Union, writers, justice
    Jan 15: Siren: Congress, elections
    Jan 17: Did Wellington flinch at Waterloo? Did Nelson cringe at Trafalgar?: Harold Wilson, Britain, austerity program
    Jan 19: Agreed...let's do something: Soviet Union, nuclear weapons
    Jan 20: I know you'll do an equally good job: Robert McNamara, Clark Clifford, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Jan 23: What shall it be, my emperor?: Congress, taxes
    Jan 26: Just in case: North Korea, USS Pueblo
    Jan 29: Blockbuster: Lyndon B. Johnson, budget
    Jan 30: Stand back, folks...I have an important announcement: Richard Nixon
  - Cartoons, 1968, Feb (Oversize 8)
    Feb 2: Wrong signal: Vietnam War
    Feb 3: Ladies and Gentlemen...I give you the new new Nixon: Richard Nixon
    Feb 5: Light in Vietnam: Vietnam War
    Feb 7: Hold it...I have an ingenious plan!: tourism, taxes
    Feb 10: Nothing personal, Mr. President: Vietnam War, Lyndon B. Johnson, Robert F. Kennedy
    Feb 12: He may have fallen into it but he hasn't come up smelling like a rose: Nelson Rockefeller, New York City, garbage strike
    Feb 13: Sign please: South Korea, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Feb 14: Are you sure you're taking me to my leader?: electoral colleges, voting
    Feb 15: Now you can play soldier without those nasty Soviet toys: Soviet Union, Jordan
    Feb 15: Fiddler on the Roof: taxes, gold reserve, Wilbur Mills
    Feb 16: The gap is very narrow indeed"...Prime Minister Wilson: Vietnam War
    Feb 17: It's surrounded by 12 foot thick skulls: civil rights
    Feb 19: New Image: Nelson Rockefeller, New York City, garbage strike
    Feb 22: He says it's up to you to make the first move: Vietnam War, Ho chi Minh, Lyndon B. Johnson, U. Thant
    Feb 23: Now here's my plan to prevent that other blowup: Vietnam War, Congress, riots, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Feb 24: Unquenchable thirst: Vietnam War
    Feb 26: I don't expect a draft but if one comes along I won't resist: Nelson Rockefeller
    Feb 29: Sorry, Rocky...I've decided to get off: George Romney, Nelson Rockefeller 1968-02-29">1 Feb
  - Cartoons, 1968, Mar (Oversize 9)
    Mar 4: Shake hands and come out fighting: Richard Nixon, Nelson Rockefeller
    Mar 5: Doc, how about cutting down on that rich stuff: healthcare, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Mar 8: But he was here last month: Eugene McCarthy, elections, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Mar 9: Independent satellite: Romania, Soviet Union
    Mar 11: Start the music: Nelson Rockefeller, Republican Party
    Mar 12: Stalemate on a stalemate: Dean Rusk, foreign policy
    Mar 16: Don't panic, folks....we're thinking of something: U.S. Dollar, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Mar 21: That's as far as I'm going to bare my assets: Senate ethics
    Mar 22: Hey, Dick...Come and get her: Nelson Rockefeller, Richard Nixon, Republican Party
    Mar 23: Falconry: Lyndon B. Johnson, Robert F. Kennedy, Hubert Humphrey
    Mar 27: He's the only one left who can beat you: Richard Nixon
    Mar 28: Don't let it get you down: cost of living, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Mar 29: I've come to save you from those big bad foreigners: textile industry, consumers, trade, congress
    Mar 30: Call of the wild: riots, demonstrations, non-violence
  - Cartoons, 1968, Apr (Oversize 9)
    Apr 3: Look what I found. How about hooking it up?: inflation, taxes, Congress
    Apr 6: The dream he never had: [U.S Capitol building being torn in two]
    Apr 9: Okay, let's start hatching: Lyndon B. Johnson, Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam War, peace
    Apr 10: It won't go out: Martin Luther King Jr., violence, racism
    Apr 11: Free at last, free at last...: Congress, housing, civil rights, ghettos
    Apr 12: Say, fellers...You sure you got the right bed?: Hubert Humphrey, labor
    Apr 16: Gee, fellers...for a while I thought I had bad breath or something: Kerner riot report
    Apr 17: Look, everybody...a groundswell: Ronald Reagan
    Apr 18: Now don't overdo it!: South Korea, peace, Park Chung-hee, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Apr 20: Required reading: government spending
    Apr 22: Stumbling block: Lyndon B. Johnson, Ho chi Minh, Vietnam War, peace
    Apr 23: What are you...some kind of a nut?: inflation, Congress, William McChesney Martin, Jr.
    Apr 25: You're not the only one who's prolific: Robert F. Kennedy, Eugene McCarthy, elections
    Apr 26: Okay, Georgie Boy...It's your BALL game: Lyndon B. Johnson, United Nations, Arthur Goldberg, George W. Ball
    Apr 27: Don't say I never did anything for you: Lyndon B. Johnson, Hubert Humphrey
  - Cartoons, 1968, May (Oversize 9)
    May 1: This time I'm in it to stay!: Nelson Rockefeller, elections
    May 2: The Kremlin wall: Czechoslovakia
    May 4: What took you so long?: Charles De Gaulle, Lyndon B. Johnson, Ho Chi Minh
    May 6: Don't tell me how to put out a fire!: Congress, taxes, inflation, Lyndon B. Johnson
    May 7: Hold still...I've decided to rescue you: taxes, Wilbur Mills
    May 8: [Editors: no caption with cartoon]: Robert F. Kennedy
    May 10: Tell them to hurry! This is an emergency!: Vietnam War, peace
    May 13: We know you're there, you trouble makers!: Poor People's Campaign, John Stennis, John McClellan
    May 17: Slow down...keep to your right...watch out ...don't fall asleep...: Vietnam War, Lyndon B. Johnson, Nguyen Van Thieu
    May 18: Eyes right: Democratic Party, Hubert Humphrey, George Wallace, elections
    May 20: The leaning tower of Pisa: Charles De Gaulle, strikes, riots
    May 21: Is there a doctor in the house?: taxes, Congress, Lyndon B. Johnson
    May 22: Charge of the Light Brigade: Ronald Reagan, Republican Party
    May 23: Just don't turn your head too quickly, mon General: Charles De Gaulle, France
    May 24: Can't you see the Doctor is busy?: Orville Freeman, farming, hunger
    May 25: Here come de Judge, here come de Judge: subversive activities control board
    May 28: We shall overcome...I think: Vietnam War, peace
    May 29: I'm only raising you three tenths of a per cent this month: consumers, inflation
    May 30: I've agreed to debate him: Eugene McCarthy, Robert F. Kennedy
    May 31: Transaction: taxes, government spending, Congress, Lyndon B. Johnson
  - Cartoons, 1968, Jun (Oversize 9)
    Jun 3: The Vietcong are clinging to two footholds in Saigon: Vietnam War
    Jun 5: Just about got her locked up: Richard Nixon, Republican Party
    Jun 8: We're cracking down on your kind!: Congress, gun control
    Jun 11: Hey, whose 'side are you on?: Supreme Court, crime
    Jun 12: I see no reason for anymore gun control bills: Everett Dirksen, crime, gun control
    Jun 12: Don't complain, we're delivering the goods!: trucking industry, transportation
    Jun 13: Trail Blazer: Nelson Rockefeller, Robert F. Kennedy
    Jun 14: You got your nerve...sneaking up on a sleeping man: hunger, William Poage
    Jun 15: Let's make our country safe from those intellectuals: George Wallace
    Jun 18: I knew WE could do it: Lee Trevino
    Jun 19: House-cleaning: housing, Supreme Court
    Jun 26: Hi, I'm Senator McCarthy. I hope I'm not intruding: Eugene McCarthy, Lyndon B. Johnson, Vietnam War, peace,
    Jun 28: Read this! What, you mean you don't know how to read?: education
  - Cartoons, 1968, Jul (Oversize 9)
    Jul 1: I will not be panicked into tighter gun-control: crime, gun control, Congress
    Jul 3: [No caption with this cartoon]: [man whispers to a woman about Fidel Castro who is sitting across the aisle]
    Jul 3: Now that I've saved you, mon general...: France, elections, economy, Charles De Gaulle
    Jul 5: Help yourself, dearie, but don't advertise this, either: tobacco industry, advertising
    Jul 6: Just stick to the script: Richard Nixon
    Jul 8: We'll disqualify them for running without mounts: Richard Nixon, Hubert Humphrey, Eugene McCarthy, Nelson Rockefeller
    Jul 9: Comrade Brezhnev, any direct talks with Israel and I'd lose face: Abdel Gamal Nasser, Israel, Leonid Ilyich Brezhnev
    Jul 11: Au revoir mon ami...someday this will be all yours: Charles De Gaulle, Georges Pompidou
    Jul 15: Parting is such sweet sorrow: Soviet Union, Czechoslovakia
    Jul 16: Steering Committee: trucking industry, Congress
    Jul 18: I'd say you need a new everything: U.S. Postal Service
    Jul 19: I'm Czeching out, Comrade: Soviet Union, Leonid Ilyich Brezhnev, Czechoslovakia
    Jul 20: Introducing our hand-picked commission to determine our salaries: Congress
    Jul 23: Very well, we'll talk at your place, Mohammed: Soviet Union, Czechoslovakia
    Jul 29: Get a horse: trucking industry
    Jul 31: Royal treatment: billboard lobby
  - Cartoons, 1968, Aug (Oversize 9)
    Aug 1: In the breadbasket: cost of living
    Aug 2: It says he's alive and well in Miami Beach: Nelson Rockefeller, Richard Nixon
    Aug 3: I said, General Hershey, you're too old for the draft: Lewis B. Hershey, Hubert Humphrey
    Aug 12: I like your direction, Gene, but I'll do my own steering: Vietnam War, Eugene McCarthy, George McGovern
    Aug 13: Chow time: trucking industry, taxes
    Aug 14: I don't understand it but our credentials are about to be questioned: Democratic Party, Alabama, Georgia, Alabama
    Aug 16: Party Unity: Eugene McCarthy, Hubert Humphrey, George McGovern
    Aug 17: Of course you understand they're samples: Eugene McCarthy, Walter Reuther, Correta Scott King, William Fulbright, Gardner Ackley
    Aug 19: Platform construction: Vietnam War, Hubert Humphrey, Eugene McCarthy, George McGovern
    Aug 20: Lester, Pay attention...see Ho run, Ho runs fast...: Lester Maddox, Lyndon B. Johnson, Ho Chi Minh
    Aug 21: Things haven't changed much in 30 years, Comrade: Soviet Union, Czechoslovakia, Adolf Hitler
    Aug 23: We're working on a new Czech government: Soviet Union, Czechoslovakia
    Aug 24: Look what I caught: Vietnam War, Eugene McCarthy, Hubert Humphrey
  - Cartoons, 1968, Sep (Oversize 10)
    Sep 5: About that campaigning, Mr. President...don't call us, we'll call you: Lyndon B. Johnson, Hubert Humphrey
    Sep 7: To teach those Russians a lesson, I've decided not to defuse: nuclear weapons
    Sep 9: Considering the circumstances I've used admirable restraint: Congress, Lyndon B. Johnson
    Sep 13: Not so hard on the Vice President, Spiro: Spiro T. Agnew, Gerald Ford, Everett Dirksen, Hubert Humphrey, communism, law and order
    Sep 14: Goodnight, David: Chet Huntley, Federal Communications Commission
    Sep 16: ...and here's some more dirt I dug up on you: Abe Fortas, Strom Thurmond
    Sep 17: Dewey was here: Richard Nixon, Hubert Humphrey, Thomas Dewey
    Sep 20: Early Foot: George Wallace
    Sep 21: The opposition: Richard Nixon, Hubert Humphrey, trucking industry
    Sep 23: I suppose another triumph for our glorious system: space exploration, Soviet Union
    Sep 24: But If I put the lid on we'd have all sorts of political fallout: nuclear weapons
    Sep 26: This is a holdup!: Abe Fortas
    Sep 28: Can't you see the balance of power will be upset if Israel gets those jets: Soviet Union, Egypt
  - Cartoons, 1968, Oct (Oversize 10)
    Oct 2: I'm just seeing to it you don't vote when you're wrong: Abe Fortas
    Oct 3: Down to size: trucking industry, Congress
    Oct 5: This is the best reception yet, Mr. Vice President: Hubert Humphrey
    Oct 7: You don't mean little Georgie Wallace?: George Wallace
    Oct 9: See, General LeMay is a man of peace: George Wallace, Curtis LeMay
    Oct 10: I'm still casting for the right face: Soviet Union, Czechoslovakia
    Oct 11: It was a tough fight but I won: World Series
    Oct 12: I'll say one thing about Hubie...he refuses to stay buried: Hubert Humphrey